Guide to the The Patty Mucha Papers MSS.342
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. 2023 Accretion, 1936-2022; 1.50 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
  - Sachs, Sid, 2013-2022 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Lichtenstein, Dorothy, 2020-2021 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Pace Gallery Correspondence, 1996-2021 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Padgett, Ron, 2013-2019 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Barry, Timothy, 2019-2020 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mandell, Pamela, 2020-2021 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Paul Dickerson Studio Art Museum (PDSAM) and Barbara Houlberg, 2007-2014 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Edwards, Karen, 1978-2018 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Gross, Mimi, 2020 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Vanderbeek Family Correspondence and Photographs, 1990-2014 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Dupuy Family Correspondence and Photographs, 1969, 2011-2021 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Stein, Judith, 1999-2021 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Provincetown -- Excerpt from "Threads" Memoir, 2021 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Harvey, Emily, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Dine, Nancy, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Irvine, Chippy, 2015-2017 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Takahashi, Hisachika, 2013-2016 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lobel, Michael, 2003-2021 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Tripp, Reeve Lindbergh, 2018-2020 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Corbett, Bill, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Cards and Photographs, 1978-2017 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Letters and Notes, 1981-2021 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Brattleboro Museum Talk, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Davis, Deborah, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Bradshaw, David, 2005, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Mucha Artwork -- Images and Promotional Material for "Gun Show", 2004, 2007, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)